<resources>

    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">DU About</string>
    <string name="hide_app_icon">Hide app</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="no_connection">Can not access without a internet connection.</string>
    <string name="general_info_title">General information</string>
    <string name="developers_title">Developers</string>
    <string name="device_title">Devices</string>
    <string name="in_beginning_title">In the beginning…</string>
    <string name="in_beginning__content">Dirty Unicorns was started at the end of 2012 by Alex Cruz. At the time he never imagined
        to see the success this project has today.\n\nThe project was created out of pressure by users of Alex Cruz\'s unofficial
        builds. At the time Alex was compiling unofficial AOKP builds for the EVO 3D and occasionally would include a mod or two
        not offered by the AOKP crew in his builds. Over time users found themselves divided. Some loved what Alex was doing while
        others were upset that they no longer had \'pure\' AOKP builds. They pressured Alex to either go back to \'pure\' AOKP
        builds or change the name.\n\nAlex approached some close friends and they discussed what was happening in his thread and so
        \'pure\' AOKP builds were dropped. With the help of close friends like Bret Zamzow, James Taylor, Josh Chasky, Barry Smith
        and a few others it began!</string>
    <string name="then_now_title">Then and now…</string>
    <string name="then_now_content">After using AOKP for a few cycles in kitkat, we decided that although we had learned a lot for
        first timers that we could do much more. We wanted a more AOSP oriented ROM base rather than one that was a mix of CAF and AOSP
        and loaded with features. We wanted a blank page or at least one that didn\'t have a lot of writing on it.\n\nWe moved on to
        OmniROM and it was great! Omni had only a few features on top of AOSP and we saw this as a great thing. We did a lot of great
        things and truly started to learn the framework. We used Omni for lollipop but we wanted more. Like with AOKP we had learned
        a lot and felt like could do more with \'pure\' AOSP.\n\nSince then we\'ve been AOSP based with a hybrid CAF branch for certain
        devices.</string>
    <string name="google_plus_link" translatable="false">https://plus.google.com/u/0/communities/109738128866939227235</string>
    <string name="twitter_link" translatable="false">https://twitter.com/_DirtyUnicorns_</string>
    <string name="github_link" translatable="false">https://github.com/DirtyUnicorns</string>
    <string name="no_contacts">No contact info found</string>

</resources>
